{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622569","name":"Elephant Room","address":"439 Congress St","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Andrew Scott","licenseNumber":"232785","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.05051,42.32813","geojson":{"id":"51622569","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.050514243,42.328126008]},"properties":{"name":"Elephant Room","owner":"Andrew Scott","address":"439 Congress St","zipcode":"48226","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"232785","establishmentid":"51622569","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"6/17/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"1387","name":"Cobo Joe's","address":"422 W Congress","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5388","name":"The Drink Hall","address":"408 W Congress","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4124","name":"Gateway Deli","address":"333 W Fort St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"240","name":"The Detroit Club ","address":"712 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1597","name":"Anchor Bar","address":"450 W Fort St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"51622912","name":"Anchor Bar ","address":"450 W Fort St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4837","name":"Zoom Coney Restaurant","address":"211 W Fort St","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4048","name":"TCF Centerl-Wayne Hall Kitchen","address":"1 Washington Blvd","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"5117","name":"TCF Centerl- Cork and Grind","address":"1 Washington Blvd","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"4049","name":"TCF Centerl-Go Gourmet/Coffee Shop","address":"1 Washington Blvd","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"50946","inspectionDate":"2020-02-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"Under the Equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"On the Equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"48923","inspectionDate":"2019-08-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\r\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\r\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\r\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\r\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\r\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\r\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\r\n\r\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution concentration","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 25 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"and the Bar","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"In the Knife rack","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"and the Bar","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-09-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"On the Equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cloths that are in use for wiping FOOD spills on TABLEWARE shall be maintained dry and used for no other purpose. \r\n(B)  Cloths in-use for wiping counters and equipment shall be held between uses in   a chemical sanitizer solution, and laundered daily.\r\n(C)  Cloths in-use for wiping surfaces in contact with raw animal FOODS shall be      kept separate from cloths used for other purposes.\r\n(D)  Dry wiping cloths and the chemical sanitizing solutions shall be free of FOOD    debris or visible soil.\r\n(E)  Containers of chemical sanitizing solutions shall be stored off the floor and         used in a manner that prevents contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, SINGLE-SERVICE, or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n(E)  SINGLE-USE disposable sanitizer wipes shall be used in accordance lable               instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wiping cloth(s)","subItem":"wet","problemDescription":"Stored on","subProblem":"Counter","location":"BAR","subLocation":"On the Counter(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-08-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"45658","inspectionDate":"2019-03-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-403.11","violationDescription":"(A)     POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD that is cooked, cooled, and reheated  for hot holding shall be reheated so that all parts of the FOOD reach a temperature of at least 165°F for 15 seconds, if  reheated in a microwave oven the FOOD must be rotated or stirred, covered, and allowed to stand covered for 2 minutes after reheating. (P)\r\n(B)  Commercially processed READY-TO-EAT FOOD shall be heated to a temperature of at least 135°F for hot holding. (P)\r\n(C) Reheating for hot holding shall be done rapidly and the may not exceed 2 hours. (P)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Reheated food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Reheated to less than 165 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"In the Steam table","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-03-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-603.11","violationDescription":"If an animal FOOD such as  beef, EGGS, FISH, lamb, milk, pork, POULTRY, or shellfish is served or sold raw, undercooked, or without otherwise being processed to eliminate pathogens, either in a READY-TO-EAT form or as an ingredient in another READY-TO-EAT FOOD, the PERMIT HOLDER shall inform CONSUMERS of the significantly increased RISK of consuming such FOODS, by using menu advisories, brochures, lable statements, table tents, placards, or other effective written means. (Pf)\r\nFOOD LAW SEC 6149\r\n...The food establishment may provide the following statement on selection information so that it is made pulblicly available: \"Ask your server about menu items that are cooked to order or served raw.  Consuming raw or undercooked, meats, poultry, shellfish, or eggs may increase your risk of foodborne illness.\"\r\nThe statements must be in a minimum of 11 point font and in a color that provides a clear contrast to background.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Menu advisories","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"OBSTRUCTED Menu","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-03-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Equipment slicer","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Slicer","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-03-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-03-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-304.14","violationDescription":"(A)  Cloths that are in use for wiping FOOD spills on TABLEWARE shall be maintained dry and used for no other purpose. \r\n(B)  Cloths in-use for wiping counters and equipment shall be held between uses in   a chemical sanitizer solution, and laundered daily.\r\n(C)  Cloths in-use for wiping surfaces in contact with raw animal FOODS shall be      kept separate from cloths used for other purposes.\r\n(D)  Dry wiping cloths and the chemical sanitizing solutions shall be free of FOOD    debris or visible soil.\r\n(E)  Containers of chemical sanitizing solutions shall be stored off the floor and         used in a manner that prevents contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, SINGLE-SERVICE, or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n(E)  SINGLE-USE disposable sanitizer wipes shall be used in accordance lable               instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wiping cloth(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on","subProblem":"Counter","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"On the Counter(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-03-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622569"}}